Register of the Gottfried Haberler papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Printed Matter III, 1927-1994
  - Policy Review, 1989 (Box-folder 101: 5)
  - "Political and Economic Interactions in Economic Policy Reform,", 1993 (Box-folder 101: 6)
  - "Proceedings of the Academy of Political Science,", 1947 (Box-folder 101: 7)
  - Rethinking our Judaism, 1986 (Box-folder 101: 9)
  - "The Rise and Fall of Vienna's Jews,", 1989 (Box-folder 101: 10)
  - The Rockefeller Foundation pamphlet, 1994 (Box-folder 101: 11)
  - Rot Weiss Rot, 1992 (Box-folder 101: 12)
  - Royal Economic Society Newsletter, 1992 (Box-folder 101: 13)
  - Schmollers Jahrbuch, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 101: 14)
  - "Schweitzerische Hochschulzeitung Revue Universitaire Suisse,", 1963 (Box-folder 101: 15)
  - Schweizerische Zeitschrift für internationale Wirtschaftsbeziehungen, 1987 (Box-folder 101: 16)
  - Shadow Open Market Committee report, 1989, 1994 (Box-folder 101: 17-18)
  - Skandinaviska Enskilda Banken Quarterly Review, 1985 (Box-folder 101: 19)
  - "Sonderabdruck aus Schmollers Jahrbuch,", 1927, 1934 (Box-folder 101: 20)
  - "Staff Studies for the World Economic Outlook,", 1993 (Box-folder 102: 1)
  - Swiss Review of World Affairs, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 102: 2-3)
  - "Ten Economists on Inflation,", 1948 (Box-folder 102: 4)
  - "Towards an Explanation of Economic Growth,", 1980 (Box-folder 102: 5)
  - "Trends in International Trade,", 1958 (Box-folder 102: 6)
  - El Trimestre Economico, 1948 (Box-folder 102: 7)
  - "Wall Street Week with Louis Rukeyser," transcript, 1992 (Box-folder 102: 8)
  - "William H. White (1922-1983) An Appreciation,", 1986 (Box-folder 102: 9)
  - Wirtschaftlichen Nachrichten, 1935 (Box-folder 102: 10)
  - World Financial Markets, 1991 (Box-folder 102: 11)
  - Zeitschrift für die gesamte Staatswissenschaft, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 102: 12)
  - "Zögerliche Konjunkturbelebung in der Industrieländern,", 1992 (Box-folder 102: 13)
- Photographs, circa 1900s-1990s
  - Friedl Haberler, circa 1950s-1990s (Box-folder 103: 1)
  - ID card photographs, undated (Box-folder 103: 2)
  - Meetings and conferences, circa 1920s-1990s, undated
    - circa 1920s (Box-folder 103: 3)
    - circa 1930s (Box-folder 103: 4)
    - circa 1940s (Box-folder 103: 5)
    - circa 1960s (Box-folder 103: 6-7)
    - circa 1970s (Box-folder 103: 8)
    - circa 1980s-1990s (Box-folder 103: 9)
    - undated (Box-folder 103: 10)
  - Portraits, circa 1970s, undated (Box-folder 103: 11; 113: 2)
  - Portraits of others, undated (Box-folder 103: 12)
  - Personal, circa 1920s-1990s
    Consists of photographs of family, friends, and vacations.
    - circa 1900s (Box-folder 103: 13)
    - circa 1920s (Box-folder 103: 14)
    - circa 1930s (Box-folder 103: 15)
    - circa 1940s (Box-folder 104: 1)
    - circa 1950s (Box-folder 104: 2)
    - circa 1960s (Box-folder 104: 3-6)
    - circa 1970s (Box-folder 104: 7 - 105: 3)
    - circa 1980s (Box-folder 105: 4)
    - circa 1990s (Box-folder 105: 5)
    - undated (Box-folder 105: 6-7)
    - travel scrapbooks, 1927-1958, undated (Box 114-121)
  - Photograph mounting corners, circa 1930s (Box-folder 106: 1)
  - Schumpeter, Joseph, with Gottfried Haberler, undated (Box-folder 106: 2)
  - Vacations slides, 1954-1972 (Box-folder 106: 3 - 107: 9)
- Friedl Haberler file, 1988-1991
  - Address books, circa 1980s, undated (Box-folder 108: 1-3)
  - Gymnastic exercises booklet, undated (Box-folder 109: 1)
  - Memorial writings and condolences, 1991 (Box-folder 109: 2-5)
  - Passport, 1983 (Box-folder 109: 6)
  - Recipe book, undated (Box-folder 109: 7)
  - Speeches and writings, 1938-1970, undated (Box-folder 109: 8 - 110: 2)
  - Stenography excercise books, circa 1970s (Box-folder 110: 3)